<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Anthems</string>

    <string name="titulo_alert">Information</string>
    <string name="button_alert">Ok</string>
    <string name="button_stop">STOP</string>

    <!-- Historia dos times -->
    <string name="gremio_hist">Grêmio is a Brazilian football club from the city of Porto Alegre,
        Rio Grande do Sul, founded on September 15, 1903. It is considered one of the biggest clubs
        in Brazil and South America. Its colors are blue, black and white. . Its biggest rival is
        Internacional.</string>
    <string name="inter_hist">Internacional is a Brazilian multi-sports club from the city of
        Porto Alegre, capital of Rio Grande do Sul. It was founded on April 4, 1909, by the Poppe
        brothers, with the aim of being a democratic institution without prejudice. Its colors are
        red and white and its fans are known as colorados. Their biggest rival is Grêmio.</string>
    <string name="cec_hist">Cruzeiro Esporte Clube is a Brazilian multi-sport association, based in
        Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais. It is considered one of the biggest football clubs in Brazil
        and South America. Founded in 1921 under the name of Società Sportiva Palestra Italia, it
        was renamed to its current name in 1942 - in reference to Cruzeiro do Sul. Its biggest rival
        is Atlético Mineiro.</string>
    <string name="cam_hist">Clube Atlético Mineiro is a Brazilian football club based in the city
        of Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais. It was founded on March 25, 1908 by a group of students,
        and its traditional colors are black and white. His most popular symbol and nickname is
        the Rooster. Its biggest rival is Cruzeiro.</string>
    <string name="cor_hist">Sport Club Corinthians Paulista is a Brazilian multi-sport club from
        the city of São Paulo, capital of the state of São Paulo. It was founded as a football team
        on September 1, 1910 by a group of workers from the Bom Retiro neighborhood. Its name was
        inspired by Corinthian FC from London, which toured Brazil.</string>
    <string name="spfc_hist">São Paulo Futebol Clube is a Brazilian multi-sport club from the city
        of São Paulo, capital of the homonymous state. It was founded on January 25, 1930, having
        interrupted its activities in May 1935, and resumed in December of the same year.
        In football, it is one of the most successful clubs in Brazil.</string>
    <string name="san_hist">Santos Futebol Clube is a Brazilian multi-sport club from the city of
        Santos, São Paulo. It was founded on April 14, 1912. Santos became in football one of
        the most successful clubs in Brazil and recognized worldwide. He became famous in the 60s
        for the various international and national championships he won and for revealing
        Pelé.</string>
</resources>